Vitaliy Polyanskiy (Full Stack Engineer)

Skype: vit.polyanskiy

E-mail: vit.polyanskiy@gmail.com

Tel.: +38 099-78- 36-817

Site: myfe.site

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vitaliy-polyanskiy-6930b515b/

Github:

• https://github.com/alreadyExisted

• https://github.com/easy-boilerplates

Summary of qualifications:

Front-end developer with a strong tech skill set and 4+ years of experience in the field of web-development.

Professional skills: native JavaScript, ES6+, TypeScript, Angular 1, ReactJS, VueJS, jQuery, Redux, RxJS, NodeJS, WordPress, HTML5, Pug, CSS3, SCSS, SASS, Stylus, Twitter Bootstrap, Gulp, Grunt, Webpack, Git, Mercurial, Jira, Confluence.

Experience:

October 2016 - Present

Front-end developer at Simcord LLC

Position: full-time web-developer.

Responsibilities:

- Development of Single Page Applications (SPA + SSR), websites according to specifications and mockups, teamwork.
- Support of existing web APPs and sites.
- Code review.
- Estimate of new projects and additional functionality.

Technologies and tools:

native JavaScript, ES6, ReactJS, Angular 1, VueJS, TypeScript, NodeJS, RxJS, Recharts, D3, Websockets, HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, SASS, Stylus, Gulp, Webpack, Git, Mercurial, Photoshop, Jira, Confluence.

Aug. 2015 – Sep. 2016

Web-developer at Startup

Position: remote full-time web-developer.

Responsibilities:

- Development of websites according to specifications and mockups, teamwork.
- Support of existing web sites.

Technologies and tools:

native JavaScript, jQuery, WordPress, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Twitter Bootstrap, Gulp, Git, Photoshop.

Languages

English – reading technical documentation.

Ukrainian – native.

Russian – native.

Education

• 2010 - 2015, H.S. Skovoroda Kharkiv National Pedagogical University, obtained Master's degree in Physics, Computer Science.

Additional information

I've released in production over 30 websites.

I have experience in developing web applications (SPA + SSR) using such JavaScript frameworks as ReactJS, Angular 1, VueJS + NodeJS.

Creation of code that is valid, cross-browser, rubber, and adaptive to different screen resolutions. Ability to work both in a team and independently. Purposeful, self-motivated, and sociable, able to work within strict deadlines, and think outside the box. I seek to constantly enhance my professional skills and adopt new practices that can benefit the quality of my work.